Alex Brenneman

Software Engineer in Kansas City, MO

I am a hard working, loyal professional with a passion for web development. Although my working experience has primarily been in the construction, metal working, and specialized skill fields, it was through this experience where I not only perfected my customer service skills, but also found a love for problem solving.

PHONE 814-521-5681 | EMAIL alexabrenneman@amail.com

GITHUB https://github.com/alexbrenneman

LINKEDIN https://www.linkedin.com/in/alex-brenneman-a09767bb/

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

ChimTech

- Personalizable customer profiles with location mapping
- Search engine for chimney finding professionals in your area
- Built using a Python, backend using Flask and MySQL for the database

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lawn and Garden Specialist — Sears Holdings, Olathe KS

Dec 2016 - Present

I am currently working as a Small Engine Repair Technician with Sears Holdings. My daily activities include, driving a company vehicle to customer's homes to repair their various machinery. I work by myself for the vast majority of the time so I have to be self motivated and creative to get things done timely and accurately. On a normal day, I will interact with between 5 and 7 different customers in their homes.

Service Technician — Curtis Chimney and Hearth, Grantsville MD

Aug 2012 - Dec 2016

My position at Curtis Chimney & Hearth required me to: Interact with multiple customers on a daily basis Work independently most days Be self- motivated to complete daily tasks Have a higher focus on safety

General Laborer — Beitzel Corporation, Grantsville MD

May 2008 - Aug 2011

My duties at Beitzel Corporation included:
General shop upkeep and maintenance
Operating shop equipment such as forklifts and other vehicles
Delivering components to job sites
Escorting oversized loads to job sites
Working with a team to complete tasks

EDUCATION:

LaunchCode, LC101 Programming Course - Graduate Fall 2018

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- Java
- Python
- · HTML5/CSS3

FRAMEWORKS

- Hibernate
- Flask

DATABASES

MySQL

TOOLS

- Intellij
- Visual Studio Code